[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Part of the idea for the character of Freddy Krueger came from a 1970s song.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Lean on Me, where was Eastside High located?", "correct_answer": "Paterson, NJ", "incorrect_answers": ["Washington, DC", "Gary, ID", "New York, NY"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What significant discovery about the nature of the constant e did French mathematician Charles Hermite make in 1873?", "correct_answer": "e is transcendental.", "incorrect_answers": ["e is algebraic.", "e^pi is transcendental.", "e is irrational"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the part of Vada, one of the main characters in the movie My Girl?", "correct_answer": "Anna Chlumsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Jaime Lee Curtis", "Terry Chiffer", "Emma Galsten"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Disney Channel movie Princess Protection Program premiered in the US on July 27, 2009.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "1973 saw the release of this full length animated film which featured the great actress Agnes Moorehead.", "correct_answer": "Charlottes Web", "incorrect_answers": ["The Voyage of Sinbad", "Just the Mouse", "The Jetsons on Vacation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A square has four unequal sides.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many trees does it  take to make one ton of paper?", "correct_answer": "17", "incorrect_answers": ["170", "34", "1100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Latin word for skin?", "correct_answer": "Cutis", "incorrect_answers": ["Derma", "Papilla", "Epicanthus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to electric power produced by running or falling water?", "correct_answer": "Hydroelectric power", "incorrect_answers": ["Nuclear power", "Aquatic power", "Hydrothermal power"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular cartoon character from a 1995 animated movie keeps a raccoon as a pet?", "correct_answer": "Pocahontas", "incorrect_answers": ["Simba", "Shrek", "Mulan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Spanish architect designed La Sagrada Familia, one of the most famous buildings in Barcelona.", "correct_answer": "Antonio Gaudi", "incorrect_answers": ["Carlo Scarpa", "Mario Botta", "Alvar Aalto"]}]